after cross-check results - len(context._results)
********** Processing logs for year: 2025
Error parsing log file w0uy.log: Improperly formatted grid locator "EM1AC". Must look like AA##, AA##AA, AA##AA##, or AA##AA##AA.
qso for AA3R found no match with K5XDD even though dx did submit a log
qso for AA5DE found no match with K5XDD even though dx did submit a log
qso for AA5UY found no match with K0FUZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for AA5UY found no match with W4BBT even though dx did submit a log
qso for AA5UZ found no match with N5RKK even though dx did submit a log
qso for AA5UZ found no match with K5QQ even though dx did submit a log
qso for AA5UZ found no match with K4SBZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for AA5UZ found no match with K3MAW even though dx did submit a log
qso for AA5UZ found no match with KT0P even though dx did submit a log
qso for AA5UZ found no match with N5JDT even though dx did submit a log
qso for AA5UZ found no match with N4QI even though dx did submit a log
qso for AB5XM found no match with AD5VC even though dx did submit a log
qso for AD5VC found no match with N5KMZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for AD5VC found no match with N4IQ even though dx did submit a log
qso for AD5VC found no match with KA0PQW even though dx did submit a log
qso for AD5VC found no match with K2AL even though dx did submit a log
qso for AD5VC found no match with KJ9C even though dx did submit a log
qso for AD5VC found no match with K8TE even though dx did submit a log
qso for AD5VC found no match with VE2GT even though dx did submit a log
qso for AD5VC found no match with K8LF even though dx did submit a log
qso for AD5VC found no match with K0FUZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for AD5VC: dx_call N8DNA was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for AD5VC: dx_call K0I was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for AE0MO found no match with K5XDD even though dx did submit a log
qso for K0AD: dx_call WW5L was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for K0CLW found no match with W5GAD even though dx did submit a log
qso for K0FUZ found no match with AA5UY even though dx did submit a log
qso for K0SV found no match with K5XDD even though dx did submit a log
qso for K0TJT found no match with KC5DI even though dx did submit a log
qso for K0TRL found no match with AA5UY even though dx did submit a log
qso for K1RO found no match with W5GAD even though dx did submit a log
qso for K1RO found no match with W5LA even though dx did submit a log
qso for K2AL found no match with AD5VC even though dx did submit a log
qso for K3MAW found no match with K5XDD even though dx did submit a log
qso for K3MAW found no match with AA5UZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for K4DR found no match with AD5VC even though dx did submit a log
qso for K4SBZ found no match with AA5UZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5MAY found no match with K5XDD even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5MAY found no match with KC5DI even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5QQ found no match with AA5UZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5VOP found no match with N5LCC even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5XDD found no match with N8II even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5XDD found no match with K0SV even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5XDD found no match with KA6BIM even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5XDD found no match with WA5SOG even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5XDD found no match with KN6VTC even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5XDD found no match with W9BLP even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5XDD found no match with K5MAY even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5XDD found no match with W4NZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5XDD found no match with N5KW even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5XDD found no match with KY7M even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5XDD found no match with N2ZZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5XDD found no match with AA5DE even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5XDD found no match with K3MAW even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5XDD found no match with KD0JTR even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5XDD found no match with KD9ZUN even though dx did submit a log
qso for K5XDD: dx_call AA3R was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for K5XDD found no match with NR0P even though dx did submit a log
qso for K8LF found no match with AD5VC even though dx did submit a log
qso for K8TE found no match with KC5DI even though dx did submit a log
qso for K8ZT: dx_call K5QQ was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for K9QC: dx_call WW5L was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for KA0PQW: dx_call AD5VC was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for KA6BIM found no match with K5XDD even though dx did submit a log
qso for KC5DI found no match with KD9WIF even though dx did submit a log
qso for KC5DI found no match with KD9MGZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for KC5DI found no match with K8TE even though dx did submit a log
qso for KC5DI: dx_call K0TJT was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for KD0JTR found no match with K5XDD even though dx did submit a log
qso for KD5BPR found no match with N4IQ even though dx did submit a log
qso for KD5BPR found no match with K0WRY even though dx did submit a log
qso for KD5BPR found no match with KA0PQW even though dx did submit a log
qso for KD5BPR: dx_call N8II was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for KD9WIF: dx_call KC5DI was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for KD9ZUN found no match with W5GAD even though dx did submit a log
qso for KD9ZUN found no match with K5XDD even though dx did submit a log
qso for KD9ZUN found no match with AA5UY even though dx did submit a log
qso for KF3G found no match with W5WZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for KF5OMH found no match with KD5BPR even though dx did submit a log
qso for KG5YPN: dx_call W0M was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for KG5YPN: dx_call N8II was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for KG5YPN found no match with N4IQ even though dx did submit a log
qso for KJ9C: dx_call NW0M was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for KJ9C: dx_call AD5VC was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for KJ9C: dx_call K0I was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for KJ9C: dx_call W5GAD was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for KJ9C: dx_call W5LA was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for KJ9C: dx_call K5QQ was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for KJ9C: dx_call WW5L was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for KM8L found no match with W5WZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for KN6VTC found no match with K5XDD even though dx did submit a log
qso for KT0P found no match with AA5UZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for KY7M found no match with K5XDD even though dx did submit a log
qso for N0HJZ found no match with WW5L even though dx did submit a log
qso for N2ZZ found no match with K5XDD even though dx did submit a log
qso for N4DW found no match with AD5VC even though dx did submit a log
qso for N4QI found no match with AA5UZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5EP: dx_call NW0M was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for N5EP: qso with NW0M was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with K5QQ was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with W2A was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with N0SS was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with N0SS was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with W7PFB was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with N0SS was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with WA0I was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with N0O was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with KOR was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with K0E was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with K0A was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with K0A was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with K0A was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with N0U was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with K0H was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with K0H was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with N0SS was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with NW0M was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with W0I was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with W0I was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with K0A was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with K0A was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with K0A was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with W0MA was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with N0LY was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with N0M was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with K0U was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with WA0I was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with N0R was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with K0H was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with K0H was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with N0SS was not valid
qso for N5EP: qso with NW0M was not valid
qso for N5JDT found no match with AA5UZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5KMZ found no match with AD5VC even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5KW found no match with K5XDD even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5KW found no match with W5LA even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5KW found no match with KC5DI even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5LCC: dx_call OM2VL was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for N5LCC found no match with K5CM even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5LCC found no match with KA6BIM even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5LCC: dx_call K5VOP was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for N5RKK found no match with AA5UZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5RKK found no match with AA5UY even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with N0HJZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with KN6VTC even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS: dx_call OM2VL was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for N5YS found no match with AE0MO even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with AJ4HP even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with W0ELT even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with W0DCN even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with N4QI even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with N3KN even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with NV4T even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with VO1GO even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with K4SBZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with KM4SK even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with N2PTF even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with W1ABK even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with K8TE even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with W4HRL even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with VE3RGO even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with W0BH even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with N8II even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with WA3KCP even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with W9QL even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with KI6KGC even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with W2CSI even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with K5YX even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with AA3R even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with VA3HYM even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with KI5KOI even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with N5RKK even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with AI5G even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with WA1SAY even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with K4SBZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with VE3YT even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with W7LG even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with WV4AM even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with K4VBL even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with K0TRL even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with W0BH even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with N5KW even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with WA2OTC even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with VE2GT even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with WN4AFP even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with KD9WIF even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with N5KW even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with N7MZW even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with KD9WIF even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with AE0MO even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with N9DEK even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with W4BBT even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with KC5LL even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with W0M even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with AD4EB even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with K9CW even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with K5MAY even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with KE0TT even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with WB9HFK even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with N5RZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with NW0M even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with N5KW even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with KC5LL even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with K5CM even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with AA5UZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with KY7M even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with KZ3P even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with KA6BIM even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with K4DR even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with K9PW even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with NV4T even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with AJ4HP even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with AC9BJ even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with WA9YI even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with NE8P even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with W4BBT even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with WA9LEY even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with N5JDT even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with K0CLW even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with WD0BRP even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with AE0MO even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with K0SV even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with AA5UY even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS: dx_call K5VOP was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for N5YS found no match with WA5SOG even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with KD0JTR even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with K0RC even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with W0PMO even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with KD9GY even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with WN4AFP even though dx did submit a log
qso for N5YS found no match with AA0CL even though dx did submit a log
qso for N8DNA found no match with AD5VC even though dx did submit a log
qso for N8II found no match with KG5YPN even though dx did submit a log
qso for N8II found no match with K5XDD even though dx did submit a log
qso for N8II: dx_call KD5BPR was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for N8II found no match with KC5DI even though dx did submit a log
qso for N8PIC found no match with WW5L even though dx did submit a log
qso for NE8P found no match with W5GAD even though dx did submit a log
qso for NR0P found no match with K5XDD even though dx did submit a log
qso for OM2VL found no match with N5LCC even though dx did submit a log
qso for OM2VL found no match with W5LA even though dx did submit a log
qso for VE2GT found no match with AD5VC even though dx did submit a log
qso for VE3JZT: dx_call N5LCC was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for W0M found no match with KG5YPN even though dx did submit a log
qso for W4BBT found no match with AA5UY even though dx did submit a log
qso for W4CRV found no match with W5GAD even though dx did submit a log
qso for W4NZ found no match with K5XDD even though dx did submit a log
qso for W5GAD found no match with K0CLW even though dx did submit a log
qso for W5GAD found no match with AA5DE even though dx did submit a log
qso for W5GAD found no match with WD0BRP even though dx did submit a log
qso for W5GAD found no match with KD9WIF even though dx did submit a log
qso for W5GAD: dx_call W4CRV was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for W5GAD found no match with K3TW even though dx did submit a log
qso for W5GAD: dx_call WA9LEY was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for W5GAD found no match with KJ9C even though dx did submit a log
qso for W5GAD found no match with KF3G even though dx did submit a log
qso for W5GAD: dx_call N4IQ was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for W5GAD: dx_call KR4AE was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for W5LA found no match with KE0TT even though dx did submit a log
qso for W5LA: dx_call N4IQ was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for W5LA found no match with K8ZT even though dx did submit a log
qso for W5LA found no match with N8DNA even though dx did submit a log
qso for W5LA found no match with K1RO even though dx did submit a log
qso for W5LA found no match with KJ9C even though dx did submit a log
qso for W5WZ: dx_call W7LG was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for W5WZ: dx_call KF3G was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for W5WZ: dx_call KM8L was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for W7LG found no match with W5WZ even though dx did submit a log
qso for W9BLP found no match with K5XDD even though dx did submit a log
qso for WA5SOG found no match with K5XDD even though dx did submit a log
qso for WA9LEY found no match with W5GAD even though dx did submit a log
qso for WA9TMU found no match with KC5DI even though dx did submit a log
qso for WB4HRL found no match with AD5VC even though dx did submit a log
qso for WB9HFK found no match with AD5VC even though dx did submit a log
qso for WB9HFK found no match with KD5BPR even though dx did submit a log
qso for WD0BRP found no match with W5GAD even though dx did submit a log
qso for WW5L found no match with K9QC even though dx did submit a log
qso for WW5L: dx_call K0AD was in all_callsigns, but nothing from qso_index_dict. COULD be a mismatch time/band/mode
qso for WW5L found no match with KJ9C even though dx did submit a log
